<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Documentations on Janusec</title>
    <link>/documentation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Documentations on Janusec</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 22:28:32 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/documentation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Start</title>
      <link>/documentation/quick-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 22:28:32 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/quick-start/</guid>
      <description>Quick Start 快速入门中文版
This document will guide you to install a Single-Node Janusec Application Gateway.
Requirements    Role Operating System Database     Master Node CentOS/RHEL 7, or Debian 9, x86_64, with systemd PostgreSQL 9.3 / 9.4 / 9.5 / 9.6 / 10   Slave Node CentOS/RHEL 7, or Debian 9, x86_64, with systemd Not required    Installation Step 1: Download  $cd ~</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>/documentation/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 08:10:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Janusec Application Gateway, an application security solutions for public cloud, private cloud, and traditional IDC, which provides web routing, load balancing, and web application firewall. With Janusec, you can build secure and scalable applications.
Janusec Application Gateway Introduction PDF
Features:  Web Application Firewall ( HTTPS support, No Agent Required )
 Load Balance Encrypted Certificates Manager Mater and Slave Nodes Supported  Make Defense Simple  SQL Injection</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>/documentation/installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 10:11:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/installation/</guid>
      <description>Installation Requirements    Role Operating System Database     Master Node CentOS/RHEL 7, or Debian 9, x86_64, with systemd PostgreSQL 9.3 / 9.4 / 9.5 / 9.6 / 10   Slave Node CentOS/RHEL 7, or Debian 9, x86_64, with systemd Not required    Step 1: Download  $cd ~
$wget https://www.janusec.com/download/janusec-latest.tar.gz
$tar zxf ./janusec-latest.tar.gz
 Step 2: Install Switch to root and run install.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Administration</title>
      <link>/documentation/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 10:11:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/admin/</guid>
      <description>Web Administration Administration Portal http://janusec_application_gateway_master_node_ip:9080/
For security reasons, use internal IP address is preferred.
You can modify the config file of the master node: /usr/local/janusec/config.json :
 &amp;ldquo;admin_http_listen&amp;rdquo;: &amp;ldquo;10.10.10.10:9080&amp;rdquo;,
&amp;ldquo;admin_https_listen&amp;rdquo;: &amp;ldquo;10.10.10.10:9443&amp;rdquo;,
 Digital Certificate Management see Certificate Management
Application Management see Application Management
Node Management see Node Management
WAF Management see WAF Management</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certificate Management</title>
      <link>/documentation/certificate-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 21:05:08 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/certificate-management/</guid>
      <description>Certificate Management Certificate List Open web administration portal and navigate to Certificate Management.
Add or Edit Certificate Single domain subdomain.yourdomain.com or wildcard *.yourdomain.com certificate are all acceptable. A wildcard certificate is preferred.
For production environment, you should have a legal digital certificate issued by a trusted CA ( such as Let&#39;s Encrypt ) .
For test purpose, when filled in the first field (Common Name or Subject Alternative Name), click Self-Sign Certificate button, it will produce a self-sign certificate for you, and you need export it with browser and add it to the trusted root CA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Application Management</title>
      <link>/documentation/application-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 21:58:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/application-management/</guid>
      <description>Application Management Requirements At least one digital certificate is required if you need https support.
Certificate Management
Add or Edit Application Open web administration portal and navigate to Application Management.
Note:
 Backend or Internal Scheme, default http and thus no certificates required in your real servers.
 Destination, IP:Port format, port is required even if the port is 80.
 Multiple destinations for backend load balancing.
 Client IP for WAF, default REMOTE_ADDR, Janusec WAF will get IP address from IP package, but if you are using Janusec Application Gateway behind a trustable CDN of third parties, usually the last IP of X-Forwarded-For should be taken, please refer to the documentation of CDN, and select relevant option, for example: the option X_Forwarded_For used for the last IP of X-Forwarded-For within the request header.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Node Management</title>
      <link>/documentation/node-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 22:38:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/node-management/</guid>
      <description>Node Management Node Type  Master Node, there must have one and only one Master Node, and a PostgreSQL is required.
 Slave Node, optional, no database required.  Single Node Architecture  One Master Node.
 No DNS Load Balance required.
 For small scale web applications.
  Multiple Nodes Architecture  One Master Node and multiple Slave Nodes Architecture.
 Only the Master Node requires a PostgreSQL database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WAF Management</title>
      <link>/documentation/waf-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 21:27:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/waf-management/</guid>
      <description>WAF Management Add or Edit WAF Policy Typical Check Points  Example: http://www.yourdomain.com/blog/show.php?id=1&amp;amp;category=2
 URLPath: /blog/show.php
URLQuery: id=1&amp;amp;category=2
GetPostKey: [id, category]
GetPostValue: [1, 2]
 GetPostKey, GetPostValue used for both GET and POST method
If you want to check url values only ( GET Only ), please select URLQuery .
 Regular Expression Janusec Application Gateway adopts Google RE2 Regular Expression . In order to simplify configuration, Janusec Application Gateway will preprocess the values to be detected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Operation Management</title>
      <link>/documentation/operation-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 21:04:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/operation-management/</guid>
      <description>Operation Management Deployment Architecture    Architecture Master Node Slave Node Description     Single-Node One None small scale applications with unified web management   Scalable One Any large scale applications with unified web management   Multiple Autonomous System Any Any Any Single or Scalable Architectures, maintained by different teams, each autonomous system has an unified web management portal.    Admin Account Web Administration address is one of the following:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Janusec</title>
      <link>/documentation/migrate-to-janusec/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 21:56:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/migrate-to-janusec/</guid>
      <description>Migrate to Janusec Application Gateway Step 1: Install and Configure Janusec Application Gateway Refer to Installation, install janusec application gateway and configure digital certificate, application.
Step 2: Hosts Test After configuration, modify you local hosts file C:\Windows\System32\drivers\etc\hosts ( not the Gateway) for test.
 the_gateway_ip your_domain_name
 Then, open web browser and navigate to https://your_domain_name.
Step 3: Modify DNS If test OK, modify your DNS setting for production, let domain name point to the gateway, and restore your local hosts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update Janusec</title>
      <link>/documentation/update-janusec/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 20:11:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/update-janusec/</guid>
      <description>Update to Latest Version Version 0.9.3 upgrade to 0.9.4 Install janusec normally, or do the following before installation.
 drop table nodes;
 and delete the line which include node_id in config.json.
 systemctl restart janusec.service
 Version 0.9.2 upgrade to 0.9.3 PostgreSQL table applications need to be updated.
The installation program will not do this operation, you should execute the following SQL command manually.
 alter table applications add column hsts_enabled boolean default true;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pricing</title>
      <link>/documentation/pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 12:00:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/pricing/</guid>
      <description> Pricing for Janusec Application Gateway    Plans Pricing License     Community Free GNU AGPLv3    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>/documentation/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 07:45:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/faq/</guid>
      <description>FAQ Q: What is the difference between Janusec Application Gateway and WAF ?  A: Janusec Application Gateway includes a WAF (Web Application Firewall), and Janusec eliminates the defects of traditional WAF.
 Q: Does it requires agent installation on business servers ?  A: No agent required.
 Q: Does it support https ?  A: Yes, https is naturally supported.
 Q: Is my private key secure ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Agreement</title>
      <link>/documentation/user-agreement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 20:38:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/user-agreement/</guid>
      <description>User Agreement and Privacy Policy  THE PRODUCT IS PROVIDED &amp;ldquo;AS IS&amp;rdquo;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE PRODUCT OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE PRODUCT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diagnose</title>
      <link>/documentation/diagnose/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 11:52:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/diagnose/</guid>
      <description>Diagnose Deployment Operating System Operating System should be x86_64 and one of the following:
 CentOS 7
 RHEL 7
 Debian 9
  Service Management systemd is used for Service Management , check :
 command -v systemctl
 (Expect result: /usr/bin/systemctl)
PostgreSQL Use psql to check PostgreSQL Connection:
 psql -h 127.0.0.1 -U janusec -W janusec
 If not OK, refer to Operation Management , PostgreSQL part.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>