<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Documentations on Janusec</title>
    <link>/documentation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Documentations on Janusec</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 14:01:34 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/documentation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Quick Start</title>
      <link>/documentation/quick-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 22:28:32 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/quick-start/</guid>
      <description>Quick Start  快速入门中文版
This document will guide you to install a Single-Node Janusec Application Gateway.
Requirements     Role Operating System Database     Primary Node Debian 9/10/11+, or CentOS/RHEL 7/8+, x86_64, with systemd and nftables (Debian 10 is prefered) PostgreSQL 10/11/12+   Replica Node Debian 9/10/11+, or CentOS/RHEL 7/8+, x86_64, with systemd and nftables (Debian 10 is prefered) Not required    Prepare nftables  nftables used for CC defense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>/documentation/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 08:10:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Introduction  Janusec Application Gateway, an application security solutions for public cloud, private cloud, and traditional IDC, which provides web routing, load balancing, and web application firewall. With Janusec, you can build secure and scalable applications.
Janusec Application Gateway Introduction PDF
 Features:  Web Application Firewall ( HTTPS support, No Agent Required ) Load Balance Encrypted Certificates Manager Mater and Replica Nodes Supported   Make Defense Simple  SQL Injection Cross-site Scripting Sensitive Data Leakage CC Attacks Block, Captcha, ByPass Policy Group Policy with Multiple Check Points   Make Administration Simple  Administration by Web Browser Integrated Administration Center   Make Architecture Scalable  Multiple Gateway Nodes   Data Protection  Private Keys Encrypted  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>/documentation/installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 10:11:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/installation/</guid>
      <description>Installation  Requirements    Role Operating System Database     Primary Node Debian 9/10/11+, or CentOS/RHEL 7/8+, x86_64, with systemd and nftables (Debian 10 is prefered) PostgreSQL 10/11/12+   Replica Node Debian 9/10/11+, or CentOS/RHEL 7/8+, x86_64, with systemd and nftables (Debian 10 is prefered) Not required    Prepare nftables  nftables used for CC defense.
nftables for Debian 10:
 apt install nftables</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuration File</title>
      <link>/documentation/configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 10:11:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/configuration/</guid>
      <description>Configuration File  Path of Configuration File  Production environment: /usr/local/janusec/config.json
Development environment: ./config.json
Configuration Items  The following is based on Janusec Application Gateway V1.0.0+, and use // as comment, please delete // comment before using it.
{&amp;quot;node_role&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;primary&amp;quot;, // &amp;quot;primary&amp;quot; for primary node, &amp;quot;replica&amp;quot; for replica nodes&amp;quot;primary_node&amp;quot;: { // keep empty for replica nodes&amp;quot;admin&amp;quot;: { // Administrator portal&amp;quot;listen&amp;quot;: true, // Listen on new ports for admin portal&amp;quot;listen_http&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;:9080&amp;quot;, // Format :port or IP:Port，when listen is true, http://IP:9080/janusec-admin/ is available&amp;quot;listen_https&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;:9443&amp;quot;, // Format :port or IP:Port，when listen is true, https://any_application_domain:9443/janusec-admin/ is available&amp;quot;portal&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;https://gate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Administration</title>
      <link>/documentation/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 10:11:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/admin/</guid>
      <description>Web Administration  Administration Portal  When listen=false in config.json :
 http://your_primary_node_ip_address/janusec-admin/ (first use) https://your_application_domain_name/janusec-admin/ (after certificate configured)
When listen=true in config.json :
  http://your_primary_node_ip_address:9080/janusec-admin/ (first use) https://your_primary_node_domain_name:9443/janusec-admin/ (after certificate configured)
 When using primary node only, any application domain name can be used for admin.
But if you have one or more replica nodes, you should apply for a seperate domain name for primary node.
Digital Certificate Management see Certificate Management</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certificate Management</title>
      <link>/documentation/certificate-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 21:05:08 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/certificate-management/</guid>
      <description>Certificate Management  Scenario: You can add and maintain the digital certificate you already have here (for example, the certificate of a corporate website).
If you don&amp;rsquo;t have a digital certificate and want JANUSEC to automatically apply for and manage a digital certificate, you can skip this section and do not need to configure it here (usually applicable to personal websites).
Certificate List Open web administration portal and navigate to Certificate Management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Application Management</title>
      <link>/documentation/application-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 21:58:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/application-management/</guid>
      <description>Application Management  Requirements If you already have a digital certificate, you can add it under Certificate Management.
If you want JANUSEC to apply for a free digital certificate by itself, you can choose to use ACME automatic certificate (free certificate) in the Domain Configuration below, and ensure that the DNS of the domain name has been pointed to the JANUSEC application gateway for the certification authority to verify the ownership of the domain name , You don’t need to add it under the certificate management (note: automatic certificates do not support wildcard domain names).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Node Management</title>
      <link>/documentation/node-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 22:38:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/node-management/</guid>
      <description>Node Management  Node Type  Primary Node, there must have one and only one Primary Node, and a PostgreSQL is required. Replica Node, optional, no database required.  Single Node Architecture  One Primary Node. No DNS Load Balance required. For small scale web applications.  Multiple Nodes Architecture  One Primary Node and multiple Replica Nodes Architecture. Only the Primary Node requires a PostgreSQL database. GSLB or DNS Load Balance required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WAF Management</title>
      <link>/documentation/waf-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 21:27:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/waf-management/</guid>
      <description>WAF Management  Add or Edit WAF Policy Typical Check Points  Example: http://www.yourdomain.com/blog/show.php?id=1&amp;amp;category=2
 URLPath: /blog/show.php
URLQuery: id=1&amp;amp;category=2
GetPostKey: [id, category]
GetPostValue: [1, 2]
 GetPostKey, GetPostValue used for both GET and POST method
If you want to check url values only ( GET Only ), please select URLQuery .
 Regular Expression Janusec Application Gateway adopts Google RE2 Regular Expression . In order to simplify configuration, Janusec Application Gateway will preprocess the values to be detected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Operation Management</title>
      <link>/documentation/operation-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 21:04:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/operation-management/</guid>
      <description>Operation Management  Deployment Architecture    Architecture Primary Node Replica Node Description     Single-Node One None small scale applications with unified web management   Scalable One Any large scale applications with unified web management   Multiple Autonomous System Any Any Any Single or Scalable Architectures, maintained by different teams, each autonomous system has an unified web management portal.    Admin Account Web Administration address is one of the following:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OAuth2 Authentication</title>
      <link>/documentation/oauth2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 23:04:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/oauth2/</guid>
      <description>OAuth2 Authentication  Introduction Janusec Application Gateway supports the following authentication：
 LDAP CAS 2.0 WeWork DingTalk Feishu Lark  Used for janusec-admin, and internal applications, for employees.
Configuration Enable authentication in Web admin UI.
How to Get UserID in Applications Janusec will add the following headers if authentication passed.
 X-Auth-Token: Access-Token X-Auth-User: UserID
 The application can use the identity authentication function without modification, and can also obtain user identity (WeWork/Dingtalk/Feishu/Lark) through X-Auth-User, or obtain further information with Access-Token (WeWork/Feishu/Lark).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Janusec</title>
      <link>/documentation/migrate-to-janusec/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 21:56:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/migrate-to-janusec/</guid>
      <description>Migrate to Janusec Application Gateway  Scenario: Migrate the published Web application to be published through the JANUSEC application gateway.
Step 1: Install and Configure Janusec Application Gateway Refer to Installation, install janusec application gateway and configure digital certificate, application.
Step 2: Hosts Test After configuration, modify you local hosts file C:\Windows\System32\drivers\etc\hosts ( not the Gateway) for test.
 the_gateway_ip your_domain_name
 Then, open web browser and navigate to https://your_domain_name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update Janusec</title>
      <link>/documentation/update-janusec/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 20:11:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/update-janusec/</guid>
      <description>Update to Latest Version   This article is only for upgrade, not for new installation.
 Latest version: v1.2.9 (Apr 03, 2022)
View current version The version information is available at admin portal, or:
 ./janusec --version
 From v0.9.10+ Update JANUSEC like this:
 #wget https://www.janusec.com/download/janusec-1.2.9-amd64.tar.gz
#tar zxf ./janusec-1.2.9-amd64.tar.gz
#cd janusec-1.2.x-amd64
#./install.sh
#systemctl restart janusec
 From V0.9.9 First, nftables is required for CC defense from v0.9.10.
nftables is not installed for CentOS 7 by default, installation is required:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pricing</title>
      <link>/documentation/pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 12:00:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/pricing/</guid>
      <description>Pricing for Janusec Application Gateway     Plans Pricing License     Community Free GNU AGPLv3    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>/documentation/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 07:45:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/faq/</guid>
      <description>FAQ  Q: What is the difference between Janusec Application Gateway and WAF ?  A: Janusec Application Gateway includes a WAF (Web Application Firewall), and Janusec eliminates the defects of traditional WAF.
 Q: Does it requires agent installation on business servers ?  A: No agent required.
 Q: Does it support https ?  A: Yes, https is naturally supported.
 Q: Is my private key secure ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Agreement</title>
      <link>/documentation/user-agreement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 20:38:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/user-agreement/</guid>
      <description>User Agreement and Privacy Policy    THE PRODUCT IS PROVIDED &amp;ldquo;AS IS&amp;rdquo;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE PRODUCT OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE PRODUCT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diagnose</title>
      <link>/documentation/diagnose/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 11:52:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/diagnose/</guid>
      <description>Diagnose  Deployment  Operating System Operating System should be x86_64 and one of the following:
 Debian 9/10/11+ (Debian 10+ is preferred) CentOS 7/8+ RHEL 7/8+  Time Please make sure the time is correct, time zone may be any.
Service Management systemd is used for Service Management , check :
 command -v systemctl
 (Expect result: /usr/bin/systemctl)
PostgreSQL Use psql to check PostgreSQL Connection:
 psql -h 127.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appendix 1: RE2 Regex</title>
      <link>/documentation/appendix-re2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 14:16:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/appendix-re2/</guid>
      <description>Appendix 1: RE2 Regex  JANUSEC Application Gateway uses Google RE2 Regular Expression 。
Regex Rule Example 1 Checkpoint: URLPath
Description: checkpoint URLPath represents the path after the domain name in the URL address, for example www.yourdomain.com/blog/show.php?id=1&amp;amp;category=2 ，URLPath is /blog/show.php
RE2 Rule:
 (?i)/\.(git|svn)/
 Description: (?i) represents case insensitive，/ represents itself, \\. matches the decimal point，(git|svn) matches git or svn, used to block access to the wrongly released source code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appendix 2: PostgreSQL Operations</title>
      <link>/documentation/appendix-psql/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 14:01:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/appendix-psql/</guid>
      <description>Appendix 2: PostgreSQL Operations  1 PostgreSQL Installation PostgreSQL is not included in the release package, you should prepare it before installation, required by the Primary Node.
Before the installation of the Primary Node, dbname, dbuser and password should be ready.
1.1 Example with Debian 10 and PostgreSQL 11  apt install postgresql
su - postgres
psql
  create user janusec with password &amp;lsquo;J@nusec123&amp;rsquo;;
create database janusec owner janusec;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appendix 3: High Availability Configuration</title>
      <link>/documentation/appendix-ha/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 14:16:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/appendix-ha/</guid>
      <description>Appendix 3: High Availability Configuration  1 Architecture Description JANUSEC Application Gateway itself supports the installation of one primary node and multiple replica nodes for load balancing.
If you need to guarantee the high availability of a single node, you can build a high availability node with keepalived.
The recommended architecture for high availability deployment is:
 deploy a master node dedicated to backend management, not open to users deploy two or more replica nodes (Replica) and install keepalived on each replica node  The following two replica nodes, assuming IP addresses 192.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
